Hanami, listen!
That octopus guy, he currently thinks that
both our domains are pushing for control.
But my goal is different from that.
I'll open up a small hole in
the barrier of this domain.
The hole that I entered through
has already been sealed.
Exiting is much harder than entering,
but I think I can still
open a hole large enough
for someone to pass
through for a few seconds.
The edge of his domain's beneath my feet.
I can tell since I
touched it when I entered.
I'm ready to go at any time.
If all three of you jump in at once.
I hope you don't have any
plans for staying behind here.
I'm risking my life.
But I don't intend to throw it away.
You two, come here!
They faced an enemy that
understood language,
so he conveyed his intent
in an indirect way,
and they put their trust
in the Grade One Sorcerer.
The previously excluded possibility of
escaping the Domain became
an option once more.
They're bolstering their
defense of the void.
That just groups them up for me to...
No!
He figured it out, but it's too late.
Get to Pushy Bureau's feet now!
The one who had inherited the
curse of the Zenin clan from birth.
and the one who could not completely cast
off that curse they both stood in witness
to the one who left it all behind now
manifested in raw flesh and taking action
huh who's that a person
a sorcerer they brought
in a new sorcerer instead
of escaping when they
had the chance hmm he's
fast he was just in midair
that's not all either
what's with his strength?
I didn't feel any cursed energy from him.
Did I just lose a
contest of pure strength?
Me, of all people?
Fushiguro, it's no good.
The hole's been sealed off.
To make matters worse, it
just figured out our goal.
And it won't let us open
a hole as easily again.
Toji...
Granny Ogami's seance technique
still continued after her death.
Her summoning of the dead should
have ceased once her grandson,
the vessel, ran out of cursed energy.
But there was no cursed
energy in the grandson's
soul that was overwritten
by Toji Zenon's body,
and his body never expended
cursed energy either.
Her technique had lost its
chance to terminate him,
and the compounding irregularities now
left her technique running rampant.
Toji Zenin was currently
fighting as directed by
his instincts until his
vessel ultimately broke.
He had become a murder machine.
This man has no cursed energy.
Not worth my attention, then.
His fangs were constantly
directed toward the strongest one.
You are my special You
are my
special
Now I know,
I'm gonna go to the city Oh,
now I'm gonna go to the city Oh,
now I'm gonna go to the city Oh, you know,
what it's wrong Me sing again I love you,
I'll call youUmmest place,
you runShut, shut down,
It should make you die your lobeable
A manga 아 You are my special It
should make you
die your lobeable
It should make you die your lobeable
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh!
Ah!
Hm…
Oh-oh-oh.
Old man...
Who is that?
He's a ghost.
Fushiguro, can you hold
out a little longer?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about this.
We're placing our bets on him.
He's smashing Playful
Cloud against itself?
He's changing in shape.
Is he sharpening it?
Am I going to lose?
Is this it?
Against a human with no cursed energy?
No.
I can feel that young
boy's domain weakening.
If I can regain my cat-miss attack
effect, I can kill them all!
I need to buy time!
Of course, you can limitate too, right?
Do I need to repeat myself again?
It's not murder!
The Domain's gone!
He seriously exercised that
octopus all by himself?
If Fushiguro hadn't shown up, we all
would have been wiped out for sure.
Although, problems still remain.
Is he an ally or not?
Huh?
How did I get outside?
His speed is incredible.
He might be faster than Sukuna.
Who is this guy?
Megumi!
You've passed on, Dagon.
Oh boy oh boy you're kidding
right this one's another level
stronger leave the rest to me old
friend stronger than Dagon our
souls will reincarnate even
without relying on human beings
let us meet again in the wasteland
a century from
now now then
first one down
next
Third one down.
It's Sukuna.
No, it's not.
The fingers.
Someone has released Sukuna's
fingers somewhere here in Shibuya.
We have to hurry, Nanako.
The fingers might draw cursed spirits.
Yeah, I know.
Please, come out, Sukuna.
Okay, you two.
Just how many fingers did you feed him?
I won't tell you. Mimiko!
That's so, then die.
Good.
The markings haven't disappeared.
This was an unexpected turn of events,
but I'll make use of it to great effect.
About Yuji Itadori, even if
he consumed all 20 fingers,
he probably still wouldn't lose
control of his body to Sukuna.
but that's only if he consumed one finger
at a time for 20
consecutive days in a row?
if he took intent at once his
body couldn't adapt fast enough!
sukuna would take control even if
it were only a temporary situation.
Wake up, Sukuna.
I fed him all ten fingers,
which means by now there should be
at least fifteen inside Yuji Itadori.
You're both still alive.
Probably due to one of their techniques.
But given how scared they are.
I doubt they can use it repeatedly.
Do not waste my time any longer!
I'll give you one second.
Move.
So this is Sukuna.
His strength is of a different
kind than even Satoru Gojo's.
It's overwhelmingly evil.
I fear that any move we make now
might result in sudden death.
breathe.
Breathe. It's okay. Breathe, right?
You won't kill us for that, right?
You hold your heads quite high.
Did you believe taking
one knee was enough?
The bows that bear most hang lowest, yes.
But I guess you guys
are pretty lightweight.
You kids first.
You wanted to speak to me.
What did you want to ask?
I'll grant you a finger's worth of time.
Now talk.
B-Below us,
there's a man in monk's robes,
with stitches across his forehead.
Please, kill him.
And also, please free Code.
Hey, Code?
Who is this Satoru Gojo?
He's strong, right?
Hmm.
The best friend I ever had.
But we had a big fight.
Haven't spoken since.
I love you.
We'll never forgive Satoru Gojo for
killing Code for as long as we live.
But we were okay with
leaving things as they were.
After all, Satoru Gojo was
Keto's one and only best friend.
But you are different.
Go to hell!
We'll make you regret this!
We know the location of one
other finger you can have.
If you kill that man for us in
exchange, we'll tell you where it is!
Please. Please.
Raise your heads up now.
Maybe go! Maybe go!
Maybe go!
I think a measly one or two fingers would
grant you the right to order me around.
Imiko!
No way I can't! Imiko!
How insulting.
Sukuna, die!
Hmm, what could this be?
A phone with some kind
of photography device.
Probably just some type of ability to
manipulate the photographed subject.
How boring.
Next, the cursed spirit.
Your turn to talk.
What is it you want?
I want...
nothing.
What's that?
Her objective was
bringing you back, Sukuna.
We just wanted your complete revival.
Right now, Itadori is
helpless to counter you.
But that is only temporary.
Of course, I'm sure you know
that better than anyone.
Even if Sukuna's reverse curse technique
is capable of healing others as well,
it can't do anything about
the shape of a soul once
it's been changed by Mahito's
idle transfiguration.
It wasn't that he didn't want
to forge a pact way back then.
It was that he couldn't forge a pact.
I see only one way forward for us.
Forge a pact with Yuji
Todori before he returns.
A pact to grant you perpetual
authority over his body.
At this moment Shibuya is
crawling with Itadori's allies.
You could use them as
leverage if you wanted to.
There's no need.
I have already devised plans of my own.
But you know, when I look at you...
All of you cursed
spirits are so desperate.
I will give you a reward as a token
of appreciation for the fingers.
If you manage to land
even a single blow on me,
I'll work under you for the time being.
And to begin, how about I
slaughter every human in Shibuya?
With the exception of one.
You'll be true to your word?
I will believe in myself,
I believe in myself.
You can still believe in myself.
The greatest
love of this world
might be something I can do with you.
Just be by yourself!
If you're going to use Jujutsu,
you should do it like this.
There are minors present.
Bury your technique.
One, two, shoot.
Please, students are watching.
I threw out papers,
so all of you through scissors
might see something good happening.
Don't suddenly try to
make this kid friendly.
Next time, Thunderclap.
I'm so drunk.